<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2016 The Android Open Source Project
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources>
    <string-array name="places">
        <item>LEGO Cars Ultimate Build Lightning McQueen</item>
        <item>Kid Connection Baby Doll Stroller Play Set</item>
        <item>Lightning McQueen</item>
        <item>Doll Accessories</item>
        <item>African American Baby Doll</item>
        <item>Mega Bloks Jeep Ride On</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="place_desc">
        <item>Jeremy, Age 9</item>
        <item>Sarah, Age 4</item>
        <item>Kevin, Age 5</item>
        <item>Maggie, Age 3</item>
        <item>Katy, Age 2</item>
        <item>Allan, Age 3</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="place_details">
        <item>LEGO Cars Ultimate Build Lightning McQueen has stunning World Grand Prix looks
            and is all set to win the race. Drive him fast and take him to victory in a flashy style.
            The golden racing rims on the wheels add style to his looks. Guido, with the Lightning McQueen flag,
            is there to cheer give the boost he needs.
        </item>
        <item>The Kid Connection Baby Doll Stroller Play Set lets children enjoy fun,
            imaginative play. It comes with a wide range of accessories, including a change of clothes,
            a diaper bag and a bottle. This baby doll stroller set makes a wonderful gift for the holidays,
            birthdays and more. It is also easy to transport and store.
        </item>
        <item>Lightning McQueen is an internationally known race car with four Piston Cup wins
            under his fan belt. He moved to Radiator Springs during his rookie year.
            The town is home to Team Lightning McQueen\'s racing headquarters, his closest
            friends, and his sweetheart, Sally. Built for power and speed, Lightning loves the
            thrill of a great race. But he\'s just as happy to slow down for a quiet cruise with good friends.
        </item>
        <item>Everything that\'s necessary for a day in a doll\'s life is here.
            Take everything your doll needs with you: toys for playtime; pretend food and milk for mealtime;
            and powder, soap and a rubber duckie for bath time. Lots of duplicate items are included for
            shopping, counting and sharing fun. This set includes even a travel pottie seat for your doll.
            The kit features: Includes 1 carrying case and 70 pieces, including: pretend food boxes,
            bottles and jars; baby bottles, dishes and utensils; toys; pretend bath and personal care products;
            1 pair of socks, 1 pacifier, and 1 pottie seat with travel pottie Take everything your dolly needs
            with you wherever you go Carrying case has bottom zip closure and easy carry handle on top.
            All products in cardboard or plastic. Not suitable for children under three.
        </item>
        <item>Isn\'t she the cutest? La Baby is a realistically looking SOFT BABY DOLL with amazingly
            detailed vinyl head, arms, and legs dressed in a cute purple outfit and matching hat.
        </item>
        <item>
            Your little 4x4 fan can take his imagination off-road and ride with the legendary Jeep
            3-in-1 Ride-On by Mega Bloks. The Jeep 3-in-1 Ride-On features iconic colors and design,
            with easy push-button controls that mimic real Jeep sounds and create an exciting ride for kids.
            The high-back seat turns the Ride-On into a walker that can easily be pushed from behind.
            Open the seat to reveal a storage compartment that can hold all 10 First Builders Jeep-themed
            blocks and more. Ideal for active children ages 1 to 3.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="place_locations">
        <item>Jeremy, Age 9</item>
        <item>Sarah, Age 4</item>
        <item>Kevin, Age 5</item>
        <item>Maggie, Age 3</item>
        <item>Katy, Age 2</item>
        <item>Allan, Age 3</item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="place_avator">
        <item>@drawable/a_avator</item>
        <item>@drawable/b_avator</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_avator</item>
        <item>@drawable/d_avator</item>
        <item>@drawable/e_avator</item>
        <item>@drawable/f_avator</item>
    </array>
    <array name="places_picture">
        <item>@drawable/a</item>
        <item>@drawable/b</item>
        <item>@drawable/c</item>
        <item>@drawable/d</item>
        <item>@drawable/e</item>
        <item>@drawable/f</item>
    </array>
</resources>
